<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">Ireland City Guide</string>
    <string name="select_a_city_for_info">Select a city for info</string>
    <string name="POSITION">POSITION</string>
    <string name="CITY_ARRAY">CITY_ARRAY</string>
    <string name="DESCRIPTION_ARRAY">DESCRIPTION_ARRAY</string>
    <string name="DESCRIPTION_FRAG">DESCRIPTION_FRAG</string>

    <string-array name="cities">
        <item>Sligo</item>
        <item>Galway</item>
        <item>Cork</item>
        <item>Waterford</item>
        <item>Dublin</item>
        <item>Kilkenny</item>
        <item>Donegal</item>
        <item>Limerick</item>
     </string-array>

     <string-array name="cities_description">
         <item> Sligo is a historic, cultural, commercial, industrial, retail and service centre
         of regional importance in the West of Ireland, and is served by rail, port and road
         links. Sligo is also a tourist destination, being situated on the Wild Atlantic Way,
         with many literary and cultural associations.
         </item>
         <item> Galway, a harbour city on Ireland’s west coast, sits where the River Corrib meets
         the Atlantic Ocean. The city’s hub is 18th-century Eyre Square, a popular meeting
         spot surrounded by shops and traditional pubs that often offer live Irish folk
         music. Nearby, stone-clad cafes, boutiques and art galleries line the winding lanes
         of the Latin Quarter, which retains portions of the medieval city walls.
         </item>
         <item> Cork is a city in south-west Ireland, in the province of Munster. As of the 2016 census,
         the city had a population of 125,657, but following a boundary extension in 2019, the
         population increased to c. 210,000. It is the second largest city in the Republic of
         Ireland.
         </item>
         <item> Waterford is a city in Ireland. It is in County Waterford in the south east
             of Ireland and is part of the province of Munster. The city is situated at the
             head of Waterford Harbour. It is the oldest and the fifth most populous city in
             the Republic of Ireland
         </item>
         <item> Dublin is the capital and largest city of Ireland. Situated on a bay on the
             east coast, at the mouth of the River Liffey, it lies within the province of
             Leinster. It is bordered on the south by the Dublin Mountains, a part of the
             Wicklow Mountains range.
         </item>
         <item> Kilkenny is a city in Ireland and the county town of County Kilkenny in the
             province of Leinster. It is built on both banks of the River Nore. The city is
             administered as a municipal district within Kilkenny County Council, although
             the Local Government Reform Act 2014 allowed for "the continued use of the
             description city". The 2016 census gave the total population of Kilkenny as
             26,512
         </item>
         <item>Donegal is a town at the mouth of the River Eske, in northwest Ireland. Originally built in the 15th century, Donegal Castle has later
             additions from the Jacobean period. The Four Masters Memorial obelisk honours
             4 scribes from the nearby Franciscan friary, now in ruins. Donegal Railway
             Heritage Centre hosts rail memorabilia in an old station house. Donegal Bay is
             home to a seal colony, plus cormorants and cranes.
         </item>
         <item>Limerick is a major city in the Republic of Ireland, set in Munster
             province in the south of the country. Its compact old town is known for
             the medieval-era St. Mary’s Cathedral and St. John’s square, which is
             lined with Georgian townhouses. Standing along the River Shannon, the
             13th-century King John’s Castle is one of the city’s most recognisable
             sites.
         </item>

      </string-array>
  </resources>
